SUMMARY

I have strong expertise in art history and math. I would like to develop other career paths in science, engineering music, creative writing and journalism. With originality, I created my own projects that execute design and functionality.

EDUCATION

College of Saint Elizabeth, Morristown, NJ

B.A., Mathematics and Arts

May 2015

HONORS/AWARDS: EOF Distinguished Achievement Award (2011-2015), Dean's List 2013, Chi Alpha Epsilon 2012 *KEY COURSES*: Art History, Graphic Design, Linear Algebra, Real Intro to Analysis, and Calculus

Columbia University Boot Camp, New York, NY

October 2020-Present

- Created creative portfolios for my various projects, such as the generate password
- Executed practices of coding, such HTML JavaScript, CSS, APIS and React
- Implemented multiple techniques for writing code in editors

PROJECTS

Password Generator | https://github.com/codeyab22/Code-Convertible-Password-Generator

- A web application designed to help users to store and generate their random password and copy into the clipboard.
- Core responsibilities included setting up the use of a password generator for user authentication and retrieving information.
- Tools Used: JavaScript, CSS and HTML

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Git/GitHub, ReactJS, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, MySQL, Bootstrap, Windows, Mac OS, Microsoft Productivity Software (Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Access)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Newark Museum, Newark, NJ

Gallery Host

September 2016-March 2020

- Supervised the gallery and reported public activities to the supervisor
- Secured the galleries and informed visitors about upcoming events
- Directed visitors to meet the events with instruction

Newark Museum, Newark. NJ

Diversifying Art Museum Initiative Leadership Intern

June 2018-December 2019

- Oversaw departments of the Museum and scheduled meetings
- Provided marketing and communication materials to created multiple projects for each department
- Participated in organizations and museum trips to learn about culture

Newark Summer Youth Program, Newark. NJ

Monitor May-August 2017

- Collected documentation and printed information for the interns
- Reviewed materials for the interns to go to their sites
- Revised and updated documentation into the system for data

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE & PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS

- Blood Drive, Girls Empowerment Mentorship, Rathskeller Event
- Student Government Association, President of Math and Computer Science Club, Vice of the Student Take Action Committee, Treasurer of the West Indian Empress Club